Guide to the Daniel A. Livingstone Papers, 1950-2001 UA.29.02.0253
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1
  - National Science Foundation General Correspondence, outdated (Box 25)
  - NSF General info (Box 26)
  - NSF Grant Proposal Schedule and Notes (Box 26)
  - NSF Grant Proposal outdated, pre-1980 (Box 26)
  - NSF Division of Biotic Systems plus resources (Box 26)
  - NSF Division of Atmospheric Sciences (Box 26)
  - NSF Doctoral Dissertation award (Box 26)
  - NSF Exchange: France (Box 26)
  - NSF Exchange: Scandinavia (Box 26)
  - NSF International Programs Misc (Box 26)
  - NSF Fellowship Opportunities in Environmental Biology for New PhDs (Box 26)
  - NSF Division of Polar Programs: Arctic Lake Process Studies (Box 26)
  - NSF Polar Program Panel (Box 26)
  - NSF Proposal Rating, 1991- (Box 26)
  - NSF Proposal Rating, 1987-1990 (Box 26)
  - NSF Proposal Rating, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Blank NSF forms (Box 26)
  - Nature (Box 26)
  - Ndoni, Paul (Box 26)
  - Newman, William A. (Box 26)
  - Nagana, Patrick (Box 26)
  - Nagana, Patrick (Box 26)
  - Nicholson, Sharon (Box 26)
  - NIH, 2000 (Box 26)
  - Nilsson, Siwtre (Box 26)
  - Njuguna, Stephen G. (Box 26)
  - NC Government Agencies (Box 26)
  - NC ECS (Box 26)
  - NC Wildlife Resources Commission (Box 26)
  - Nyamweru, Celia (Box 26)
  - N Misc, Current year (Box 26)
  - N Misc, 1996- (Box 26)
  - N Misc, 1991-1996 (Box 26)
  - N Misc, outdated (Box 26)
  - Obeng, Leticia E. (Box 26)
  - Odei, M.A. (Box 26)
  - Ogden, J. Gordon (Pete), III (Box 26)
  - Okayo, Daniel O. (Box 26)
  - Okun, Dan: Lake Victoria Project (Box 26)
  - Oldfield, F. (Box 26)
  - Olmstead, Ingrid (Box 26)
  - Olsen, Paul E. (Box 26)
  - Opdyke, Neil (Box 26)
  - Dr. Neil D. Opdyke (Box 26)
  - Opuni, E. K. (Box 26)
  - Organic Petrology (Box 26)
  - ORSTOM (Office de Recherche Scientifique et Technique Outre-Mer) (Box 26)
  - Osmaston, H. A. (Box 26)
  - F. Owen (Box 26)
  - O Misc., Current year (Box 26)
  - O Misc., 1991 (Box 26)
  - O Misc., 1990 (Box 26)
  - Paepe, Roland (Box 27)
  - Pages (Box 27)
  - Paleobiology (Box 27)
  - Paleobiology Program (Box 27)
  - Paleolimnology: John Smol (Box 27)
  - Paleolimnology Symposium, 1985 (Box 27)
  - Palynos (Box 27)
  - Parashkevov, Yavor (Box 27)
  - Patrick, Ruth (Box 27)
  - Patterson, Graeme (Box 27)
  - Pearson, Daniel (Box 27)
  - Pearson, Ginny (Box 27)
  - Pechenik, Jan A. (Box 27)
  - Peirce, J. jeffrey (Box 27)
  - Perdue, Tony (Box 27)
  - Perkins, Ronald (Box 27)
  - Perrot, Alan (Box 27)
  - Perry, Linda (Box 27)
  - Personnel: Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Personnel: Work Study Project Descriptions (Box 27)
  - Personnel: Employee Information (Box 27)
  - Personnel: Job Descriptions (Box 27)
  - Personnel: Job Applicants (Box 27)
  - Pesacretas, George (Box 27)
  - Peters, Hans M. (Box 27)
  - Petersen, Richard R. (Box 27)
  - Petr, Tomi (Box 27)
  - Pew Scholarship (Box 27)
  - Pilbeam, David (Box 27)
  - Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 27)
  - Pokrywka, Gregory S. (Box 27)
  - Porter, Philip W. (Box 27)
  - Porter, Wanatha (Box 27)
  - Posnansky, Merrick (Box 27)
  - Possible Postdocs (Box 27)
  - Powers, Dennis (Box 27)
  - Prell, Warren (Box 27)
  - Prentice, Colin (Box 27)
  - Progress in Phyiscal Geography (Box 27)
  - Publishers and Book Dealers (Box 27)
  - Puga, Karen (Box 27)
  - Pulliam, Julie (Box 27)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1985-1999 (Box 27)
  - Quaternary Research (Box 27)
  - Quaternary Research: Steve Porter (editor) (Box 27)
  - Q Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Radiocarbon Dating Laboratory, University of Miami (Box 28)
  - Raisbeck, Grant (Box 28)
  - Rajagopal, R. (Box 28)
  - Rampino, Michael (Box 28)
  - Rapu, Victoria K. (Box 28)
  - Raven, Peter H. (Box 28)
  - Reeves, C. C. Jr. (Box 28)
  - Reeves, Rick (Box 28)
  - Reimann, Karen (Box 28)
  - Reinthal, Peter (Box 28)
  - Reller, L. Barth (Box 28)
  - Remington, Charles L. (Box 28)
  - Renault, Robin (Box 28)
  - Renvoize, Steve (Box 28)
  - Richard, Pierre (Box 28)
  - Richards, John (Box 28)
  - Richards, Keith (Box 28)
  - Richardson, Jonathan and Alic (Box 28)
  - The Rift Valley of East Africa: Highlights of Current Seismic Reflection Work (Box 28)
  - Rifts et Fosses Anciens (Box 28)
  - Riley, Gordon A. (Box 28)
  - Ritchie, Jim C. (Box 28)
  - River boat pump instructions (Box 28)
  - Robbins, Brian and Norrie (Box 28)
  - Roche, Emile (Box 28)
  - Rode, Sandra (Box 28)
  - Rosenthal, Bruce (Box 28)
  - Rosenthal, Bruce: Deep Drilling DUML Oceanography Cooperative Plan (Box 28)
  - Rosenthal, Steve (Box 28)
  - Roth, Louise (Box 28)
  - Rowland, Mary M. (Box 28)
  - Rowland, Michael M. (Box 28)
  - Ruddiman, Wm. F. (Box 28)
  - Ruddle, Frank H. (Box 28)
  - Ruden, Fridtzov (Box 28)
  - Rzoska, Judith (Box 28)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1996-current year (Box 28)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1985-1995 (Box 29)
  - Safety (Box 29)
  - Samoa (Box 29)
  - Sanders, Nancy (Box 29)
  - Schaak, Sarah (Box 29)
  - Schalke, H. J. W. (Box 29)
  - Schindler, D. (Box 29)
  - Schindler, J. (Box 29)
  - Schmidt, Peter (Box 29)
  - Schold, Gary P. (Box 29)
  - Scholz, Chris (Box 29)
  - Schopf, Tom (Box 29)
  - Schuurman, Gregor (Box 29)
  - Science (Box 29)
  - Scott, Louis (Box 29)
  - Scroggs, Roxanne (Box 29)
  - SECID Conference, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Sellers, Susie (Box 29)
  - SEM use: DAL (Box 29)
  - Semazzi, Fred (Box 29)
  - Sept, Jeanne (Box 29)
  - Servant, Simone (Box 29)
  - Shaffer, Mark (Box 29)
  - Sharp, Ed (Box 29)
  - Shaughnessy, Ed (Box 29)
  - Shaw, Duncan (Box 29)
  - Sherwood, Matthew: Work-Study, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Shinnie, P. L. (Editor Nyame Akuma) (Box 29)
  - Shipping, Kenya, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 29)
  - Sigmon, Kristina (Box 29)
  - Societas Internationalis Limnologiae (SIL), 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Silander, John A. (Box 29)
  - Simpson, Beryl B. (Box 29)
  - Skinner, Susan (Box 29)
  - Slaiby, Barbara (Box 29)
  - Slobodkin, L. Basil (Box 29)
  - Smart, Chuck (Box 29)
  - Smit, J. K. and sons (Box 29)
  - Smith, Sharon (Box 29)
  - Smithsonian Panel, 1995-1996, undated (Box 29)
  - Smol, John (Box 29)
  - Snyder, Lex (Box 29)
  - Sowunmi, M. A. (Box 30)
  - Spear, Ray (Box 30)
  - Sponsored Programs: Announcements, etc. (Box 30)
  - Stager, Curt (Box 30)
  - Stanley, Daniel (Box 30)
  - Stanley, Edward A. (Box 30)
  - Stearns, Donald (Box 30)
  - Steinwascher, Kurt F. (Box 30)
  - Stinchcombe, John (Box 30)
  - Stoffers, Peter (Box 30)
  - Stratton, Alice (Box 30)
  - Stuchlik, Leon (Box 30)
  - Sugden, Jean (Box 30)
  - Sugihava, George (Box 30)
  - Swain, Mike (Box 30)
  - Symoens, J. J. (Box 30)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1987-1999 (Box 30)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1983-1986 (Box 31)
  - Table Ronde on Rifts (Box 31)
  - Talbot, Michael (Box 31)
  - Talbot, Michael: Bosumtwi, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Talbot, Michael: Hydrogen Index (Box 31)
  - Talbot and Kelts: Carbonates in Bosumtwi (Box 31)
  - Talling, J. F. (Box 31)
  - Tanganyika TB, Burundi (Box 31)
  - Tanganyika, L.: TB-1 (Box 31)
  - Taub, Frieda B. (Box 31)
  - Taylor, David (Box 31)
  - Taylor, Peter (Box 31)
  - Teeri, James (Box 31)
  - Teledyne Isotopes (Box 31)
  - Terborgh, John (Box 31)
  - Tesha, P. (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Doug (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Keith (Box 31)
  - Tieszen, Larry (Box 31)
  - Tietze, Klaus (Box 31)
  - TILLMIAP (Box 31)
  - Townsend, R. M. (Box 31)
  - Travers, Christine (Box 31)
  - Tropical Freshwater Biology (Box 31)
  - Tsukada, Matsuo (Box 31)
  - TUCC-DAL Records (Box 31)
  - TUCC-DAL Accounts (Box 31)
  - Tucker, Alice H. Estes (Box 32)
  - Tutin, Winifred (Box 32)
  - T Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - UFFRO (Box 32)
  - UNESCO (Box 32)
  - United Airlines (Box 32)
  - Universities Council on Water Resources (Box 32)
  - US-Israeli Binational Science Foundation (Box 32)
  - United Touring Company, Nairobi, Kenya (Box 32)
  - U Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - van Campo, Madame Madeleine (Box 32)
  - Van Damme, Dirk (Box 32)
  - van Geel, Bas (Box 32)
  - Vareschi, Ekkehard (Box 32)
  - Vaz, Louise (Box 32)
  - Verschuren, Dirk (Box 32)
  - Vertices (Box 32)
  - Villa, Paola (Box 32)
  - Vincens, Annie (Box 32)
  - Visa Applications (Box 32)
  - Vogel, Kevin (Box 32)
  - Von Herzen, R. P. (Box 32)
  - Vuilleumier, Francois (Box 32)
  - Vulis, Inna (Box 32)
  - V Miscellnaeous (Box 32)
  - Wagner-Dobler, Irene (Box 32)
  - Waithaka, David (Box 32)
  - Walker, Donald (Box 32)
  - Walter, Bob (Box 32)
  - Ward, David (Box 32)
  - Washburn, Lincoln (Box 32)
  - Watson, Wendy C. (Box 32)
  - Webb, T. and J. H. Andrews: Corresponding Patterns of Contemporary Pollen and Vegetation in Central North America (Box 32)
  - Weigl, Peter (Box 32)
  - Weinstein Evron, Mina (Box 32)
  - Weitzel, Pamela (Box 32)
  - Weiss, Karl (Box 32)
  - Wendorf, Fred (Box 32)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation (Box 32)
  - Wetzel, Robert G. (Box 32)
  - Wheeler, Elizabeth (Box 32)
  - White, Richard (Box 32)
  - Whitehead, Donald R. (Box 32)
  - Whiteside, M. C. (Box 32)
  - Whyte, Samuel (Box 32)
  - Wickens, G. E. (Box 32)
  - Wielemaker, W. G. (Box 32)
  - Wilbur, Bob (Box 32)
  - Wilbur, Henry M. (Box 32)
  - Wilbur, Karl (Box 32)
  - Wilhalf, Diane M. (Box 32)
  - Williams, Martin (Box 32)
  - Williamson, P. G. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, E. O. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Will (Box 32)
  - Work-Study Students (Box 32)
  - Wright, H. E. (Box 32)
  - Wright, Kerry (Box 32)
  - Wrobel, David (Box 33)
  - Wyckoff, Peter (Box 33)
  - W Miscellaneous (Box 33)
  - Yato, Joseph (Box 33)
  - Yemane, Keddy (Box 33)
  - Yuretich, Richard (Box 33)
  - Zenith (Box 33)
  - Zinderen Bakker, Eduard van (Box 33)
  - Zogning, Appolinaire (Box 33)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous (Box 33)
  - Correspondence (Box 36)
- Office Files, 2
  - Hayes, Wilmot, Livingstone, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: fishes NS, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: mastodon, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Hayes et al P32, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: orientation, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Hayes, Livingstone: trout, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: pollen Alaska, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: sampler, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: pollen valley fill, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: sigmoid growth phase, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone BR Godwin, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: speculations biology fossil midge abstr, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone: yeahohs possum, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone, Bryan, Leahy, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone, Livingstone, 1958 (Box 1)
  - [Volta Lake] (Box 6)
  - Melack Ghana Field Notes (Box 6)
  - Ghana Field Notes (Box 6)
  - Narvasha (?) Crater Lake (Box 6)
  - Maar Lakes of Uganda (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Light Data (?), 1971 (Box 6)
  - Xerox of Sally MacIntyre Field Books--Kenya, 1976 (Box 6)
  - [Narvasha] (Box 6)
  - [Field Notes] (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - Dahlem Conference (Box 6)
  - INQUA, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Symposium on Great Lakes, April 1975 (Box 6)
  - ASLO, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Conference Files (6 folders) (Box 6)
  - Records of Nairobi Trip, 1979 (Box 6)
  - SIL-UNEP Workshop on African Limnology, December 1979 (Box 6)
  - Abundance Maps of Maritime Trees, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Smithsonian Advisory Council for Systematic and Environmental Biology, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Geology Review Panel (Box 6)
  - RIVFLO Program (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Oil Shale Panel (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Oil Shale Panel (4 folders) (Box 7)
  - Caracas Ms., 28924 (Box 7)
  - Association for Tropical Biology (Manaus) (Box 7)
  - Caracas (Association for Tropical Biology; 2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Paleolimnology Symposium (Mikolaiki) (Box 7)
  - INQUA (Box 7)
  - NSF Teaching Grant (Box 7)
  - [Duke Research Council] (Box 7)
  - [Grants Binder: Confirmation, Budget Changes, Memos] (Box 7)
  - Dynamics of Productivity in Tropical African Lakes (Box 7)
  - Lab Letters (Box 7)
  - Bujumbura Letters (Box 7)
  - Africa Field Letters, 1971 (Box 7)
  - General Letters, 1968-1971 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence-4th Grant (Box 7)
  - Budget Revisions-4th Grant (Box 7)
  - Code Transfers (Box 7)
  - Dynamics of Tropical Pleistocene Ecosystems (Box 7)
  - Grant Proposal (Box 7)
  - [Staff Files] (Box 7)
  - [NSF Grants] (Box 8)
  - INQUA (Box 8)
  - Maritime Archaic Seminar (Box 8)
  - NSF Polar Programs Panel (Box 8)
  - NSF Borrow Trip (Box 8)
  - L. Mikolaiki (Box 8)
  - INQUA (Box 8)
  - Oil Shale Panel-Correspondence (Box 8)
  - Human Origins Conference (Box 8)
  - Minnesota Trip, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Quarternary Geography of Africa and the Theory of Rainforest Refugia Ms. (Box 8)
  - 5th International Palynological Conference, 1980 (Box 8)
  - GIF-SUR-YVETTE Meetings (Box 8)
  - DDW Report (Box 8)
  - FAO Rome (Box 8)
  - INQUA Moscow (Box 8)
  - Deevey Symposium, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Climate Symposium (Fairbridge) (Box 8)
  - Sedimentation in the African Rift System (London), 1984 (Box 8)
  - Kokamega (?), 1985 (Box 8)
  - Desmond Clark Conference (Box 8)
  - EPA-DOE Atm. Polution RTP, 1986 (Box 8)
  - AP News Council (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Boulder Mtg (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - INQUA Congress-Ottawa (Box 8)
  - Snowbird Meeting, 1988 (Box 8)
  - S. Carolina (Box 9)
  - MM Notes, 1992 (Box 9)
  - African lectures--miscellaneous, undated (Box 9)
  - Lectures (2 folders), 1988 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Maps (Box 9)
  - Stratigraphy (Box 9)
  - Kilham Lecture, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - OH transparencies not used at Makokola I (Box 9)
  - EOS lecture, 2007 (Box 9)
  - unlabeled folder (Box 9)
  - 2002 Lectures Tropical Limnology (Box 9)
  - Rick Battarbee (Box 9)
  - Guadalajara talk (Box 9)
  - Scholarships, etc. (Box 9)
  - Makokola II keynote (Box 10)
  - Itinerary--Club Mak II (Box 10)
  - Makokola II keynote Water [Chem?] (Box 10)
  - Eric Odada (Box 10)
  - Meeting agenda (Box 10)
  - Club Mak II accounts (Box 10)
  - Paleolimnology queens, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Waterloo, 2000 (Box 10)
  - [Beuning?] Grass meeting (Box 10)
  - APD Nairobi, Oct 22-25, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Berlin Bosomtwe Meeting, 2001 (Box 10)
  - NAS Smithsonian Research, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Committee on Smithsonian Scientific Review, Final Committee Meeting, July 30-31, 2002 (Box 10)
  - IDEAL--Tallahassee (Box 10)
  - Bosomtwe, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Tour, 2006 (Box 10)
  - IDEAL, 1993 (Box 10)
  - IDEAL, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - IDEAL, 1990 (Box 10)
  - ASLO Santa Fe (Box 10)
  - ASLO Santa Fe, 1997 (Box 10)
  - ASLO Symposium, 1993 (Box 10)
  - IDEAL (no longer current) (Box 10)
  - IDEAL-Jinja (Box 10)
  - World Bank (Box 10)
  - Great Basin Symposium, May 1993 (Box 10)
  - Pyramid Lake Abstracts (Box 10)
  - Potsdam Meeting (Box 10)
  - AAG Charlotte, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Berne Workshop (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Hawaii Meeting, May 27-June 2, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Hawaii Trip (Box 11)
  - Hawaii Workshop Handout Sheets (Box 11)
  - Penrose Conference (Box 11)
  - Nairobi Meeting (Box 11)
  - Nairobi Biodiversity Meeting, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Database Workshop (Box 11)
  - IDEAL Steering Committee, 34881 (Box 11)
  - IDEAL, 1996 (Box 11)
  - AAAS Philadelphia, 1998 (Box 11)
  - IDEAL, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Teresa Hart Meeting, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Hart Meeting (Box 11)
  - SIL Dublin, 1998 (Box 11)
  - IDEAL 1999 (Box 11)
  - Durham IDEAL Workshop, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Inaugural Univ Coll Dublin, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Paris Database, 1996 (Box 12)
  - IDEAL, October 1996 (Box 12)
  - ASLO Santa Fe (Box 12)
  - Notes on N. S. Minnow Distr, Collecting Methods, and Bibliography from Dr. Dymond, Royal Ontario Museum of Zoology, 1947 (Box 12)
  - early notebooks (3), 1950s (Box 12)
  - CEGAL alpha files A-D (Box 34)
  - CEGAL alpha files E-Z (Box 35)
- Classes, 3
  - Biology 110 (four folders) (Box 1)
  - Ecology, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Biology 110 (two folders) (Box 1)
  - Ecology TAS, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Biology 110, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Biology 11, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Ecology, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Really old biogeochem (Box 1)
  - GEH Factors (Box 1)
  - Tropic Dynamics (Box 1)
  - Productivity (Box 1)
  - Cycles (Box 1)
  - Ecology Notes, 1992 (Box 1)
  - [Zoology 103] (Box 1)
  - Biology 110 Lab Handouts-Misc. (Box 2)
  - Biology 110, 1992 (Box 2)
  - [Biology 110], 1991 (Box 2)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access restricted.
  - [Biology 110], Fall 1990 (Box 2)
  - Biology 110-Ecology, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Zoology 103, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Zoology 103, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Ecology 103 (9 folders), 1976-1985 (Box 2)
  - Zoology 103, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Ecology Class (four folders), 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Mimeographical Material for Ecology Class (Box 2)
  - Zoology 103, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Ecology Class, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Ecology Class-Records, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Limnology, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Limnology Papers (Box 2)
  - Limnology-Old Exams (Box 2)
  - Limnology Handouts (Box 2)
  - Limnology Lab Exercises (Box 2)
  - Limnology, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Biology 216, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, Spring 1979 (Box 3)
  - Limnology, 1976 (Box 3)
  - 2-minute lectures (Box 3)
  - O49S (Global Change Seminar), 2001 (Box 3)
  - B. Archie: E. A. Wildlife Course (Box 3)
  - [Unlabelled Scientific Journal Articles] (Box 3)
  - UPE 302, 2002 (Box 3)
  - UPE 302, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - UPE 301, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - UPE 302, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Ecology Seminar, 2002 (Box 3)
  - UPE 301, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Ecology Class (UPE 301), 2000 (Box 3)
  - Global Change Seminar, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Paleoecology, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Paleoecology Papers (Box 3)
  - Seminars, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Paleoecology, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Paleoecology, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Paleoecology, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Ecology, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Ecology, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Ecology, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Ecology, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Seminar, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Pleistocene Ecology Seminar, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Paleobiology, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Zoology 218, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Zoology 218, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Pleistocene Seminar, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Pleistocene Ecology (Zoology 356-9), 1970 (Box 4)
  - Pleistocene Seminar, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Pleistocene Seminar, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Boring Seminar File (DAL's class records drawer) (Box 4)
  - Independent Study, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Summer Fall 1975, Spring 1976 (Box 4)
  - Fall 1974 Spring 1975 (Box 4)
  - Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - Chemical Ecology, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Biogeography Lectures (Box 4)
  - Old Limnology Lab Instructions, etc. (Box 4)
  - David Frey Papers (Box 4)
  - Other Bay Lake Papers (Box 4)
  - WEB Maps (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Limnology, 1957 (Box 4)
  - General Biology Lab Exercises (Box 4)
  - Quantitative Ecology Seminar (Box 4)
  - Peter's Zoo 1 Course (Box 4)
  - Oceanography (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Zoo 1 General (Box 4)
  - Lecture notes, 1962-1983 (Box 34)
  - Class notes (Box 34)
- Grants, 4
  - 3rd African Grant NSF GB-3567, May 1, 1965 - April 30, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Cavalier Shipping Co. (Box 4)
  - Field Correspondence, September-December 1972 (Box 4)
  - Field Correspondence, January-September 1963 (Box 4)
  - Weidlich-Letters from Sally (Box 4)
  - NSF Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (Box 4)
  - Grant Annual Reports (Box 4)
  - OKEDI-EAFFRO Laboratory (Box 4)
  - East African Freshwater Fisheries Research Organization (Box 4)
  - Bedford Landrover papers and letters, 1971, 1973-197? (Box 4)
  - Grant Proposal-Xerox Copy (Box 4)
  - Misc-Correspondence (Box 4)
  - International Biological Program (Box 4)
  - Lab Personnel (Box 4)
  - Instructions Notes regarding John Melack's outstanding orders (Box 4)
  - Sally MacIntyre (Box 4)
  - John Melack (Box 4)
  - Kenya (Box 4)
  - Ethiopia (Box 4)
  - Tanzania (Box 4)
  - Uganda (Box 4)
  - NSF: Dynamics of Productivity in Tropical African Lakes (Box 4)
  - NSF: African Climate During the Last Ice-Age (Box 4)
  - African Climate During the Last Ice-Age (8 folders) (Box 5)
  - South Seas (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Debert Coring Project (Box 5)
  - Alaskan Trip, Summer 1974 (Box 5)
  - NSF: Paleobiology of Grasses Proposal, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Ghanaian Plans (Box 5)
  - [Kenyan Research] (Box 5)
  - National Museum of Canada (Box 5)
  - [Turbulent Mixing in Lakes] (Box 5)
  - [African Lakes Research] (Box 5)
  - UNESCO Paper (Box 5)
  - Ghana Trip (Box 5)
  - Environmental Impact of Tropical Dams (Box 5)